retrogames.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for ZTNet,L.L.C. and it's Network of sites: 

**ZTNet** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ZTNet](http://www.ztnet.com/) and [www.ztnetstore.com](http://www.ztnetstore.com/)

This information is inclusive of all ZTNet Hosted Sites, unless otherwise stated at that site. 

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We use the IP address and other generic information (Browser and Operating System Version) to generate statistics for our hosted websites.

#### Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We also use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Our messaging system uses cookes so users do not have to re-enter their password many times while reading and responding to messages. 

In addition, our online store uses cookies to maintain the consistancy of the items in your shopping cart as you navigate the store.

#### Advertisers 

ZTNet, L.L.C. works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Adtegrity manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on our network, please go to [Adtegrity Privacy Policy](http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp). 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

#### Personal Information 

All of our web sites do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted, unless otherwise specified by a separate privacy policy. 

Our online store collects only relevant information persuant to verifiying your identity when submitting credit card information, and ensuring the product is shipped to the proper location. This information will not be used to contact you with anything aside from your purchase. 

#### External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **ZTNet** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. The only logged information is accessable only to administrators with logins to our internal servers. 

## Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
